本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧字幕 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
《反恐24小时》前情提要
Previously on 24
我去去就回
I'll be right back.
蕾妮
Renee!
天哪
Oh, God...
你说你有一份视频文件能证明
You said you had video file implicating people inside
杀害蕾妮的是俄罗斯政府里的人
the Russian government who were responsible for Renee's murder.
我要那份文件
I want that file.
告诉我文件在哪  快说
You're gonna tell me where that file is, now!
在一个银行保险箱里
It's in a safety deposit box!
在哪
Where?
第一联合储蓄
First Unity Savings.
蕾妮的死跟我一点关系都没有  杰克
I had nothing to do with Renee's death, Jack.
别动
No.
你还想耍花招  不是吗
You never give up, do you?
也许沃什就在鲍尔手里
Bauer may have Walsh,
但他还没拿到证据
but he can't have the evidence yet.
我们还有机会阻止他
We've still got a chance to stop him.
不止我一人有证据证明
I'm not the only one who can prove that elements
贵国政府内有人阴谋破坏和平进程
in your government conspired to undermine the peace process.
所以你希望我来替你干掉杰克·鲍尔
So you expect me to kill Bauer for you?
你有专干这行的秘密杀手
You have the covert assets here to do the job.
或许我是有
Maybe I do.
但我没有相关资源来找到并跟踪他
But I don't have the resources to find him.
反恐小组有
CTU does.
而且那里负责搜捕的人现在都归我管
And the man in charge of the search now reports to me.
我们发现他了
We got him.
一旦他们抓到鲍尔
Once they have Bauer,
我就会得知他们把他关在哪里
I'll find out where they're holding him.
我们趁着他被关押干掉他
You'll have to take him out while he's in custody.
站住  警察
Freeze! Police!
不许动
Do not move.
杰克  告诉我  我还能做什么
Jack... tell me what I can do.
用不着
Nothing.
翻译： 化石鱼     罗玉凤     插线     hodala     叶eve
■
时间轴：马姑娘     校对：何何     罗玉凤     我是无辜的     插线
后期：冰河     特别鸣谢：咖啡    冰卡     监制：何何
■
以下事件发生于中午十二点到一点间
The following takes place between 12:00 P.M. and 1:00 P.M.
蒙德  我是沃莱基队长
Mund, this is Captain Walleki.
我在现场  你把那人从银行带过来了吗
I'm on scene. You got that guy from the bank yet?
报告队长  我正带他上来
Just bringing him up, Captain.
好的
Right.
他叫科尔·奥迪斯
His name's Cole Ortiz.
他说他是反恐小组的
And he says he's with CTU.
你当时和这个女人在银行
You were with this woman at the bank.
你能告诉我她是谁吗
You can tell me who she is?
她叫丹娜·沃什
Her name is Dana Walsh.
她被近距离射中两枪
Shot twice at close range
其中一枪  近弹孔处留有大量弹药残留物
lot of powder residue around one of the entries,
就像是被执行了死刑一样
like an execution.
谢了  蒙德  带他去反恐小组
Thank you, Mund. Get him to CTU,
现在就去
now.
刺杀哈桑的行动已万事俱备
The hit on Hassan is all arranged.
巴扎耶夫及其手下正在处理一切
Bazhaev and his people are taking care of everything.
很高兴听到这些
Well, I'm pleased to hear it,
但你打个电话告诉我不就行了
but you could have just as easily called to tell me that.
我想知道你是否已向上级请示
I wanted to know if you've spoken to your superiors...
这事一完我就金盆洗手了
told them that I'm out after this goes down.
我反映了你的要求
I told them what you wanted.
他和我的感受一样
He feels the same as me:
我们对你投入太多  不能让你就此退出
we have too much invested in you to let you walk away.
你应专注于把电磁脉冲设备带进反恐小组
You should be focused on getting the E.M.P. device into CTU,
而不是你的男友奥迪斯
not on your boyfriend, Ortiz.
他是我的未婚夫  我说了别把他卷进来
He's my fiance, and I told you to leave him out of this.
我警告过你离他远点  但你不听
I warned you to stay away from him, but you didn't listen.
现在你对他动真情了吗
And now you think you have feelings for him?
你觉得你爱上他了  要嫁给他吗
You think you love him, going to marry him?
是的
Yes.
我要嫁给他
I am.
如果你无法接受这个事实的话
And if you have a problem wrapping your brain around that fact,
也许我该找你莫斯科的头儿谈谈
maybe I should talk to your boss in Moscow.
你只能和我单线联系
You talk to no one but me.
就此打住
We're done here.
哈桑死之前不许再联系我
Don't contact me again until Hassan is dead.
喂
Yeah?
是我  给你发了一个dat格式的视频
Hey, it's me. I sent you a DAT video file.
收到了  正在上传
I got it. It's uploading right now.
我需要你帮我查出视频中那名男子的身份
Okay, I need you to get me an I.D. of the man in the video.
另外  我在逃亡中
Also, I'm coming in hot,
你必须想尽办法避免暴露你的系统
so whatever you have to do to protect your systems from getting flagged, do it now.
那个女人呢  也需要查明身份吗
What about the woman? You need an I.D. on her?
她已经死了  一会儿见
She's dead. I'll see you in a few minutes.
好吧
All right.
杰克·鲍尔最后出现在
Jack Bauer's last known location
莱克星敦市的第一联合储蓄银行
was First Unity Savings Bank on Lexington,
警方收到报警  显然是丹娜·沃什打的
where police responded to a 911 call, apparently from Dana Walsh.
现在她死了  鲍尔杀了她
She's dead now. Bauer killed her.
从犯科尔·奥迪斯协助了鲍尔
Cole Ortiz, who is known to be aiding and abetting Bauer
他正被带过来接受审讯
is being brought here for questioning.
现在我需要大家别再管联合国安全事务了
Now, I need everybody not committed to the U.N. Security task
集中全部精力找到鲍尔
to devote their full attention to finding him.
我需要对所有的摄像头画面进行面部识别
I want all cameras routed through facial recognition
并监听所有的电话
and all phone calls monitored.
要是带宽不够
You don't have the bandwidth,
就从别的任务那里腾出来用
you steal it from other tasks.
要是发现任何线索  立刻向我汇报
If you think you have a lead, you bring it to me immediately.
有问题吗
Any questions?
他们为什么要去银行
Why did they go to the bank?
丹娜说过她有俄罗斯人刺杀哈桑的证据
Dana said she had evidence of Russian involvement in Hassan's murder.
也许她就把证据藏到那了
Maybe that's where she was stashing it.
根本没有证据  这一点总统已不予考虑
There's no evidence; the president dismissed this.
但她带着杰克去银行是为了去取东西
Well, she went to the bank with Jack to get something.
没错  她取的是个爆炸装置
Yeah, what she got was an explosive device
此装置能让她趁机逃跑
that made possible her escape.
这自始至终就是她设计好了的
It was her plan all along.
听着  杰克·鲍尔不能接受
Look, Jack Bauer can't accept the fact
仅丹娜·沃什一人为伊斯兰共和国中
that Dana Walsh was an enemy agent working solely
哈桑政府的反对派们卖命这一事实
with the I.R.K. opposition to Hassan's government.
蕾妮·沃克的被害让他悲痛至极
His... grief over Renee Walker's murder
导致他胡思乱想  认为这是俄当局的阴谋
is causing him to create this fantasy about a Russian conspiracy.
事实就这么简单  他失去了理智
The simple truth is, he's lost it,
他不仅危及自身  还危及整个社区
and he's a danger to himself and the community.
所以大家别再对本次行动充当事后诸葛了
So let's stop second-guessing the operation,
还是赶紧找到他吧
and find him.
事情越发不对劲了
Something is seriously wrong here.
皮勒正无视最关键的问题
Pillar's ignoring the key questions,
他根本就是在答非所问
and the questions that he is answering, no one's asking.
你想说什么
What are you getting at?
我认为杰克是对的
I think Jack's right:
这是个试图隐瞒真相的阴谋  皮勒也有份
this is a cover-up, and Pillar's involved.
银行里确实有证据  现在杰克拿到了
That evidence was at the bank, and Jack has it.
你敢确定吗
You don't know that.
都是猜测而已  可能事情就像皮勒说的那样
It's all speculation. It may be just like Pillar says.
除非我知道其它情况  否则我只按命令行事
Until I know otherwise, I got my orders.
没被发现
I'm clear.
你刚没开玩笑
Well, you weren't kidding.
你确实在逃亡中
You said you were coming in hot.
所有的警用步话机里都在讨论你
All the police scanners are talking about you.
他们说你射杀了一个女人
They said you shot and killed some woman.
就在东部贫民区的一个建筑工地
Construction site on the East Side.
是你发给我的视频里的那个女人吗
Is that the same woman in the video you sent me?
没错  查出那男人的身份了吗
Yeah. Did you I.D. the man?
没有  除非你告诉我到底发生什么了
No. I'm not going to, either...
否则我不帮你查他的身份  杰克
till you tell me what the hell is going on, Jack.
你看过那段视频了
You saw the video.
丹娜·沃什是俄罗斯间谍
Dana Walsh is a Russian operative.
她协助了此次暗杀哈桑总统行动和核弹袭击事件
She facilitated the assassination of President Hassan and the dirty bomb attack
要是我们没及时阻止  整个上西区都将被夷为平地
that would have wiped out the entire Upper West Side if we hadn't stopped it.
我不关心也不想知道今天发生什么了
I don't want to know about what happened today, and I don't care;
我想知道为何你一个人单枪匹马
I want to know why you're out there on your own
为什么大家都在抓你
and why everybody's after you.
因为总统想把我关起来
Because the president tried to lock me down.
-为什么  -因为我知道她试图掩盖
- Why?  - Because I know she's trying to cover up
今天的袭击与俄方有关这一真相
the Russian's involvement in today's attack.
那你干嘛不逃之夭夭
Then why didn't you disappear?
因为我办不到
Because I can't!
听着  杰克  我想帮你
Listen, I want to help you, Jack.
真的想
I really do.
我要你对我开诚布公
I need you to be straight with me.
实话告诉我到底发生什么了
Tell me exactly what's going on.
俄罗斯人夺走了我的所爱
The Russians took something from me.
她叫蕾妮·沃克
Her name was Renee Walker.
他们就在我的公寓里杀害了她
They killed her inside my apartment.
我要让他们血债血偿
And I need to make them pay.
好吧
All right.
事实上  我确实查出了那个人的身份
Actually, I did I.D. the guy.
就是他  帕维尔·托卡列夫
There he is: Pavel Tokarev.
俄情报部门首席特工
Primary operative, Russian intelligence.
他现在在哪
Where is he?
具体我也不清楚
I don't know exactly.
目前在美国境内
He's in the USA.
一月以前靠外交签证入境的
Came in a month ago on a diplomatic visa.
外交签证
Diplomat.
我试图访问俄大使馆的数据库
I tried to access the Russian database in the embassy.
他没在领事馆出现过
He didn't show up in the consulate.
所以说不好他在哪  杰克
He could be anywhere, Jack.
为保密起见  他们必须得小队行动对吧
To keep everything quiet, they'd have to be a small unit, right?
对
Yeah.
我有办法了
I think I've got an idea.
给我接条安全线路
Get me a secure line.
梅瑞狄斯  没想到你还在这
Meredith. I didn't expect you'd still be here.
还有几个关于哈桑的新闻发布稿要审校
Oh, fact check called: there are a few items left on the Hassan piece.
艾比可以帮你继续跟进报道啊
Abby can follow up on it for you.
我知道  只是...我想确保一切都没问题
I know. I just... I need to make sure it's right.
我知道他对你很重要
I know what he meant to you.
从你写的这篇文章就看得出来
It shows in this piece you wrote.
他的确是个伟人
What a great man he was.
你已经还他公正了
You've done him justice.
希望如此
I hope so.
-里德小姐  3号线有你的电话  -谢谢
- Miss Reed, there's a call for you on 3. - Thank you.
如有何需要  请尽管告诉我
Let me know if there's anything you need.
谢谢  加里
Thanks, Gary.
我是梅瑞狄斯·里德
This is Meredith Reed.
里德小姐
Miss Reed.
-你是谁  -我叫杰克·鲍尔
-Who is this? -My name is Jack Bauer.
请别声张  听我说
Please don't say anything; just listen.
那些你认为该对哈桑总统的死负责的人
The people that you think are responsible for killing President Hassan
他们不是单打独斗
were not working alone.
他们得到俄当局内部人士的资助
They were being funded and managed
并受他们操纵
by people working inside the Russian government.
你怎么知道的
How do you know this?
我有证据  是打入反恐组内部的
I have proof of this: a video file that was made
俄方间谍留下的一个视频文件
by a Russian agent working out of CTU.
她做这文件的初衷是为求自保
She made it for her own protection.
视频可以解释过去24小时发生的一切
It explains everything that happened in the last 24 hours.
你和当局取得联系了吗
Have you contacted the authorities about any of this?
我不能去  我被人陷害了  就像你昨天一样
I can't. I'm being set up, just like you were yesterday.
我得把这证据交给你
I need to get this evidence to you.
特纳百货公司3楼  有一间咖啡厅
There's a coffee stand on the third floor of Turner's Department Store.
你看20分钟内你能赶到吗
Do you think you can get there in the next 20 minutes?
里德小姐
Miss Reed...
昨天是我帮你洗脱了罪名
yesterday I helped clear your name.
现在该你帮我洗清冤屈了
Right now I need you to help clear mine.
拜托了
Please.
我当然会帮你
Of course I'll help you.
我也和你一样迫切想要了解真相
I-I want to know the truth as much as you do.
谢谢
Thank you.
请坐
Take a seat.
鲍尔在哪
Where's Bauer?
不知道
I don't know.
你现在麻烦大了  科尔
You're in some trouble here, Cole.
我想你应该清楚
I assume you're aware of that.
不过幸运的是
Luckily for you,
我能解决你所有的麻烦
I'm in a position to make all that go away.
我看过你的档案
I reviewed your record.
到目前为止  简直可以说是模范
You've had a exemplary career up to now.
你就是皮勒
You're Pillar.
没错
That's right.
杰森·皮勒
Jason Pillar.
我受命于总统  负责监督缉捕杰克的行动
I've been asked by the president to oversee the effort to retrieve Jack Bauer.
总统阁下
Madam President?
对
Yes.
这么说你也是帮忙掩盖真相的
So you're a part of the cover-up?
我看到档案里写道  你在费卢杰服过役
Oh, I see here you served in Fallujah.
我本人也曾两度
I-I spent two tours
指挥过驻巴古拜的海军陆战队行动小组
in command of a marine unit in Baquba myself.
我们都是军人
We're both soldiers.
所以你应该明白  当最高统帅
So you understand, when the commander-in-chief
认为此次行动是为了国家利益
deems a course of action necessary to the national good,
那我们就无权质疑
it's not our place to question it.
事实上  我们是同一阵营的
The truth is: we're on the same side.
我们都是为了国家至高利益考虑
We both want what's best for our country.
鲍尔才不关心那些
Bauer doesn't care about that.
他对你的遭遇也丝毫不在乎
He didn't give a damn about what happened to you,
只要满足了他的需求即可
just as long as it served his needs.
他利用了你
He used you.
我再问你一次
So let's start over.
你知道杰克·鲍尔在哪吗
Do you know where Jack Bauer is?
可能在某处吧  手里掌握着你们
Probably somewhere with the evidence you guys
想极力掩盖的证据
keep saying doesn't exist.
跟我耍花招没有好下场的
You really don't want to be playing with me.
什么事
What?
好消息  我们可能有鲍尔的线索了
Good news, we may have a line on Bauer.
我们窃听到一个电话
We intercepted a call.
最后一次机会
Last chance.
如果再执迷不悟  谁也救不了你
You don't take it, there's nothing anyone can do for you.
把他带走收押
Take him to holding.
阿洛从国安局梯队情报系统获得了
Arlo got a cell phone intercept report
一份手机监听报告
of NSA's Echelon.
关键词是  哈桑  俄罗斯政府  杰克·鲍尔
Key words are Hassan, Russian government, Jack Bauer.
-阿洛听到对话内容了吗  -暂时还没
- Did Arlo hear any of the conversation? - No, not yet--
目前他只是在处理数据
all he's got so far are the data handles,
但他已经在进行声音识别了
but he's processing the voice matrix now.
能确定是鲍尔吗
Are we sure it's Bauer?
暂时还不能  但是电话的另外一方
No, not yet, but the other side of the call
登记的是  梅瑞狄斯·里德
was a phone registered to Meredith Reed.
她是反恐组昨晚抓的那名记者
She's the reporter CTU arrested last night
是在第一次暗杀哈桑之前抓的
before the first attempt on Hassan's life.
有传言说她是哈桑的情妇
Rumor has it she was also his mistress.
如果鲍尔要把证据交给其他人的话
If Bauer was going to reach out to someone with the evidence,
她肯定是首选
she would be an excellent choice.
阿洛  先放下手头的工作
Arlo, stop what you're doing.
给监听内容做好警示标记并加密上锁
Tag and lock the intercept download
然后直接传到伊登的系统里
and send it directly to Eden's system.
-由她来接手  -没必要  长官
- She'll take it from there. - That's not necessary, sir.
我叫你让伊登来处理  谢了  阿洛
I said I want Eden to handle it. Thanks, Arlo.
有一个视频文件
There's a video file that was made
是打入反恐组内部的俄方间谍留下的
by a Russian agent working out of CTU.
她做这文件的初衷是为求自保
She made it for her own protection.
视频可以解释过去24小时发生的一切
It explains everything that happened in the last 24 hours.
你和当局取得联系了吗
Have you contacted the authorities about any of this?
我不能去  我被人陷害  就像你昨天一样
I can't. I'm being set up just like you were yesterday.
我得把这证据交给你
I need to get this evidence to you.
特纳百货公司3楼  有一间咖啡厅
There's a coffee stand on the third floor of Turner's Department Store.
你看20分钟内你能赶到吗
Do you think you can get there in the next 20 minutes?
是杰克·鲍尔
Jack Bauer.
我们确定了声纹
We confirmed the voiceprint.
这么说...
So...
他下一步棋就是把证据送媒体曝光
take it to the press-- that's his next move.
看来是的
It appears to be.
以里德与哈桑的关系
Reed's connection to Hassan means
她打心眼里愿意帮助杰克
she'd be highly motivated to help him.
杰克还没给她看过什么  对吧
And he hasn't shown her anything yet?
-没有  长官  -那就是说
- No, sir. - Which still means that we,
我们仍然不知道到底是什么证据
we don't know what the evidence actually is.
反正我们很快就会把证据搞到手的
Well, it will be in our hands soon enough.
这是一个扫除一切障碍的大好时机  长官
This is a major opportunity to make everything go away, sir.
鲍尔和证据
Bauer and the evidence.
我已经派遣了俄方行动小组前往那里
I've already dispatched the Russian ops team to the location.
他们会在杰克和里德见面之前就位
They'll be in position well before the meet.
你得摆平当地的执法部门
You need to deal with local law enforcement,
确保帕维尔能施展拳脚
make sure Pavel has room to move.
我们正把纽约警局的人调离那里
Yes, we're deploying NYPD away from the site,
但我们仍需要你们的人尽可能地速战速决
but we'll still need your guys in and out as quickly as possible.
明白了
Understood.
杰森  这是你们取得的重大突破
Jason, this is, this is a major break you've got,
这是决定性的突破
a major break.
谢谢  长官
Thank you, sir.
我们会把事办妥的
We'll shut this down.
我想亲自监督此事  米哈伊尔
I want to stay on top of this personally, Mikhail.
你能把帕维尔的电话号码给我吗
So will you let me have Pavel's number?
能让这房间有点私密空间吗
Can you make this room less public?
你找我有何吩咐吗
You wanted me for something?
对  你拦截到的那个电话
Yeah, the call you intercepted--
就是皮勒强行插手的那个
the one that Pillar hijacked--
你觉得是杰克打来的吗
do you think it was from Jack?
无法确定
I can't be sure.
程序筛选出的关键词是  哈桑  核  鲍尔
The program hit on keywords Hassan, nuclear, Bauer,
但这三个词在过去几小时内都在新闻上出现过
but all three have been in the news in the last few hours.
可这电话是打给梅瑞狄斯·里德手机的
But the call was to Meredith Reed's cell phone.
她是一名追踪报道哈桑人物传记的记者
She's a journalist with an interest in the Hassan story.
所以有很多人会给她打电话
Plenty of people could be calling her.
不一定非得是杰克
Doesn't have to be Jack.
好吧  那这个怎么解释
Okay, then explain this.
电话截获报告刚发到这里
Cell intercept report comes in here.
而两分钟之后
Two minutes later
皮勒就把整个对话录音下载到一个独立服务器
Pillar downloads the entire conversation into a segregated server
并且安装有我从未见过的防火墙
surrounded by firewalls like I've never seen.
知道他后来又做了什么吗
Then what does he do?
拨出了  一个  两个  三个电话
Call one, call two, call three.
机主: 皮勒  保密线路
Pillar Restricted
他会打给谁
Who'd he call?
我不知道
I don't know.
均超出了反恐组的监控范围  且全部加密
They're outside of CTU and they're all completely masked.
所以现在问题是  如果这电话无关紧要
So the question is this: if the call was nothing,
那他们为什么还要掩饰
then why are they still hiding it?
若这电话是杰克打来的
If the call was Jack,
那他们为何还不派出反恐组特警队
then why haven't they dispatched CTU SWAT team?
又为何不向纽约警局发警报
Why haven't they alerted NYPD?
阿洛  他们也参与了企图掩盖真相的阴谋
Arlo, they're in on the cover-up.
看看他们
Look at them.
更糟的是  他们正打算干掉杰克
What's worse is, they're planning on taking Jack out.
为什么  为什么他们要那么做
Why? Why would they want to do that?
因为他知道的太多了
Because he knows too much.
他已拿到了丹娜的证据
He's gotten a hold of Dana's evidence,
从而证明俄当局介入了暗杀哈桑的行动
which proves the Russian involvement in Hassan's assassination.
他们不能让他把真相公之于众
They can't let him go public with that.
因此我要找到他  而我需要你的帮助
That's why I have to find him, and I need your help.
好吧
Okay.
你想怎么干
How do you want to do it?
我要去跟科尔谈谈
I'm gonna talk to Cole.
在过去两小时里  他一直跟杰克和丹娜在一起
He just spent the past two hours with Jack and Dana.
他一定知道杰克想干什么
He must have some idea of what Jack's up to.
皮勒在时刻监视科尔
Pillar's got Cole continuously monitored.
你不可能偷着溜进去的
You can't get in there without being seen.
我们来剪辑一段循环视频
We'll create a loop
插入到监控录像的信号中
and graft it into the security feed.
我们就会碰到另一个问题
That's the other problem:
他们在我们系统上增加了一层额外的监控
they added an extra layer of oversight to our system.
我试图进行超越我安全许可的操作时
Second I try to move beyond my security clearance,
我屏幕上就会出现警告
I get an on-screen warning.
他们在监视着我们的一举一动
They're watching everything we're doing.
那好吧
Okay, fine.
我们这么办  创建一个无线信号发射点
We'll use this, create a mobile hot spot.
那样我们就可以用独立网络而不用受皮勒监视
That way we can work off our own net without Pillar breathing down our necks.
明白
Got it.
正在配置备用网络
Setting up alternate network now.
接入网络了
We're up.
好了  我正在限制对你我的访问
Okay, I'm restricting access to you and me.
循环录像的时长是多长
How long will it take you to make the loop?
只能给你90秒的时间
I can only give you 90 seconds.
一超时  就会有人发现
Anything more than that, somebody will notice.
好吧  你设置好了给我发信息
Okay, text me when you're set up.
画面起始及循环点已记录
Start Loop Point Logged
录制中  最大时长  90秒
Recording: 90 Seconds Maximum Time Allowed
弗雷德里克斯  麦克德蒙特被电磁脉冲弹炸伤了
Fredericks, McDermott was injured in the E.M.P. Blast,
我需要你把夜班卡给我收好
so I need you to collect the night shift time cards
送到我办公室来
and take them to my office.
好的
Okay.
可否现在就去
Like now?
是  长官
Yes, ma'am.
你有90秒的行动时间  -阿洛
You're clear for 90 seconds. -Arlo
我们给监控信号插入了循环录像
We put a loop in the security feed.
我只有90秒时间
I've only got 90 seconds,
所以我得直扑主题
so I'm gonna get straight to the point.
我要找到杰克
I need to find Jack
-不然他们会杀了他  -谁要杀他
- or else they're gonna kill him.  - Who's gonna kill him?
皮勒和他的部下
Pillar and whoever is working with him.
你得告诉我他在哪
You need to tell me where he is.
我不知道
I got no idea.
你和他都在银行
You were at the bank with him;
他一定说过什么
he must have said something.
听着  杰克出尔反尔说一套做一套
Hey, what Jack says and what he does are two very different things.
他要去揭穿阴谋  披露真相
He's trying to expose the cover-up.
他才不管什么企图掩盖真相的阴谋呢
He doesn't give a damn about any cover-up.
他要把所有与蕾妮的死有关的人统统杀光
He's taking out anyone who was anywhere near Renee's death,
首先拿丹娜开刀
starting with Dana.
她已经给了他证据  可他还是杀了她
She gave him the evidence and he killed her anyway.
她拿了保险箱里的枪
She took the gun out of the safety deposit box.
他朝她近距离平射
He shot her point-blank.
杰克处决了她  正如她所预料的
He executed her, just like she said he would.
整件事里根本就没有好人
There are no good guys here.
杰克  皮勒  让他们互相残杀
Jack, Pillar... they end up killing each other,
也许才是最好的结局
maybe it's the best thing.
不行  杰克是我的朋友
No, Jack's my friend.
如果我能找到他  我就能说服他
If I can find him, I can talk him down.
而这些人只会去要他的命
These people are just going to kill him.
我需要你站在我一边
I need you to be on my side.
所有人都想要拉拢我
Everybody wants me on their side.
我却又为谁而战呢
Who am I fighting for?
如果我们能找到他
If we can get to him,
我们就能揭穿这个掩盖真相的阴谋
we can expose the cover-up.
你就待在这里继续自我忏悔吧
You just stay here and feel sorry for yourself.
我自己去找他
I'm gonna go find him.
等等
Wait.
听着  我知道的不多  杰克可能有个帮手
Look, it's not much, but Jack's got to be working with someone.
谁
Who?
我不知道  我没见过他
I don't know; I never saw him,
但从杰克配备有最尖端的武器和通讯系统判断
but Jack showed up with state-of-the-art weapons and comms,
他一定在城里有联络人
so he's got to have a contact in the city.
你要想找到杰克
You want to find Jack,
得先找到这个帮手
you find his supplier.
谢谢
Thanks.
阿洛
Arlo.
出来得很及时  你没事吧
You got out in time. You okay?
是的  我没事
Yeah, I'm okay.
听着  我知道杰克的动向了
Listen, I know what Jack's doing.
调出他的档案  把他在三州交界的联系人
Pull up his files, get me the list of his known associates in the tri-state area,
还有他以前的同事的名单给我
anyone he's worked with in the past.
好的
Okay.
在接下来的半小时里
In the next half hour,
被广泛认为是和平协议的
the man who has widely been acknowledged
"关键的第三方"人物
as the vital "Third partner" in the peace process--
俄国总统尤里·萨瓦洛夫
Russian President Yuri Suvarov--
将飞抵肯尼迪国际机场
will touch down at JFK.
他将转乘直升机前往曼哈顿
He'll be ferried into Manhattan by helicopter
之后会前往联合国大厦
and then to the U.N.
喂
Yes.
帕维尔  请报告最新情况
Pavel, update, please.
我的小队已就位
My team is in position.
发现鲍尔了吗
Any sign of Bauer?
还没有
Not yet.
我需要知道
I need to know.
怎么处理那女人
What about the woman?
那女人
The woman?
就是那个记者  怎么处置她
The journalist, her disposition.
里德女士一直协助和煽动恐怖活动
Ms. Reed is aiding and abetting a terrorist.
她对我们两国都是个严重的威胁
She's a serious threat to both our countries.
你看着办
Do what you have to.
我从伊桑的笔记上看到我们仍未彻底解决
I see from Ethan's notes that we still have not completely resolved
检查团通行许可的问题
the issue of site access for the inspection teams.
我认为这问题已经解决了
I believe it was resolved.
哈桑总统同意了
President Hassan agreed
观察员将获得在全国的通行许可
the inspectors would have right of passage over our entire country.
但是他将学校列在范围之外
But he exempted schools.
只有小学
Only primary schools.
奥马可不认为
Omar didn't think
10岁小孩会去造核弹
ten-year-old children would be building nuclear missiles.
当然不会
Of course.
我想起来了
I remember now.
我深表歉意
I-I do apologize.
您没事吧  总统阁下
Are you all right, Madam President?
今天太漫长了
It's been a long day.
我很好  谢谢
I'm fine. Thank you.
总统阁下
Madam President.
请恕我失陪几分钟
If you'll excuse me for a few minutes,
我有人要接见
there's someone I need to see.
当然可以
Of course.
他在哪
Where is he?
他在会议室  总统阁下
He's in the conference room, ma'am.
感谢您能和我见面  总统阁下
Thank you for seeing me, Madam President.
我有好消息
I have good news.
我们掌握了鲍尔的方位
We've located Bauer.
我手里有证据  但...
He-He has the evidence, but...
查尔斯  你向我保证过
Charles, you assured me
事情不会走到这一步
that that wouldn't happen.
请让我说完
Please, let me finish.
我们知道鲍尔将会现身的确切位置
We know exactly where Bauer will be
和确切时间  而且此时此刻
and when, and-and we have an operation underway
我们已经展开了对他的抓捕行动了
to reacquire him even as we speak.
相信我  这是个好消息
Believe me, this is good news.
事情一完就立刻通知我
Let me know as soon as it's resolved.
我要回去谈判了
I need to get back to the negotiations.
还有件事  总统阁下
Just... There's just one thing, Madam President.
还有三个小时就要签署条约
Uh, we are three hours away from the signing of the treaty.
我在这次和平进程中扮演的角色
Isn't it time for my role in the process
是否该获得官方承认了
to be officially recognized?
我在想的是类似于...
I was thinking some kind of, uh,
向媒体发布一份声明
announcement to the media,
或许由您的新闻秘书发布
perhaps by your press secretary,
甚至由您亲自宣布也可以  总统阁下
or maybe even by you yourself, Madam President.
您该记得我们协商好
It was, you'll recall, our agreement
我会以官方身份出现在这历史性的一天
that I would have a public face on this historic day.
我相信这是我应得的
I believe I've earned it.
我会告诉我的新闻秘书
I will talk to my press secretary.
她会在一点的新闻上及时发表这份声明
She will make the announcement in time for the 1:00 o'clock news.
非常感谢  总统阁下
Thank you very much, Madam President.
已接触目标
We have contact.
目标直奔三楼的电梯处去了
Target heading to the third floor escalator.
收到
Acknowledged.
我看见她了
I see her now.
已锁定里德
We have eyes on Reed.
确认是里德
Reed is confirmed.
二号和三号小组  里德正向你处靠近
Units 2 and 3, Reed is approaching you.
请确认
Confirm contact.
确认是里德
Reed confirmed.
正向约定地点靠近
Approaching the meeting place.
-发现鲍尔了吗  -他在哪
- Any sign of Bauer? - Where is he?
他该在现场
He should be here.
没有发现
No sign.
-帕维尔  发现鲍尔了吗  -还没
- Pavel, do you see Bauer? - Not yet.
一号小组  请报告
Unit 1, report.
我们没有看见鲍尔
We have no visual of Bauer.
杰森  你去哪
Jason, where are you going?
发现他了  他正要去...
There he is. He's heading up towards...
各小组注意  鲍尔在三楼  你们看见他了吗
All units, bauer is on the third floor. Do you see him?
没发现
I do not have him.
什么  他就在那里  我们看见他了
What? He's there. We see him.
把眼睛睁大点  该死
Get your eyes open, damn it!
我还是没看见他
I have not seen him.
发现他了
Got him.
鲍尔从西南角处  快接近目标了
Bauer is approaching the target from the southwest.
身穿棕色皮夹克和牛仔裤
He's got a brown leather jacket and jeans.
他在那
There he is.
帕维尔  他已在视线范围内
Pavel, he's in view.
他快要到咖啡厅了
He's closing in on the cafe.
你应该已对他有清晰的瞄准视野了
You should have a clean line on him.
帕维尔  有机会就开枪
Pavel, if you have a shot, take it.
我看见他了
I've got him.
把枪放下
Put it down.
上面都处理好了  杰克
Everything's all clear up at the top, Jack.
收到  跟我走
Gopy that. Come with me.
照我说的做
Do exactly what I say.
各小组注意  目标已暴露  把他干掉
All units, target is in the open. Take him out.
重复  把他干掉
I repeat, take him out.
-蹲在这  别动  -好的
- You stay down here. You don't move. - Oh, okay.
-别动  -好的
- Don't move! - All right.
-走  -好的
- Move! - Okay.
刚刚到底发生了什么
What the hell just happened?
他知道这是个陷阱
He knew it was a trap.
别让他们脱离视线
Don't let them out of your sight.
我们跟丢他了
We lost him.
继续找
Just keep looking!
你开枪杀的是些什么人
Those people you shot-- who were they?
-俄国间谍  你有问题吗  -没有
- Russian operatives. You have any problems? - No.
我们走
Let's move.
杰森  说吧
Jason. Tell me.
恐怕我得告诉您一个坏消息  长官
I'm afraid I have bad news, sir.
帕维尔的小队全军覆没
All of Pavel's team is dead,
帕维尔也被鲍尔抓走了
and Bauer has Pavel.
他从一开始就比我们捷足先登  长官
He was ahead of us from the get-go, sir.
他肯定早料到我们会使用梯形情报系统
He must have anticipated that we'd use Echelon,
然后他设计了一系列关键词
and he put out a series of keywords,
并料到监听站会截获这些关键词
knowing the listening stations would pick them up.
他耍了我们  长官
He played us, sir.
他知道我们会动用非常规人员来对付他
He knew we'd use off-book resources to deal with him.
他利用那个记者引蛇出洞
He used that journalist to draw them out.
长官  现在情况的严重性已不言而喻
Now, sir, I hardly need to tell you that the situation is grave.
帕维尔知道一切
Pavel knows everything.
他安插了沃什  他主导了俄方的一系列行动
He ran Walsh, he set up the Russian ops.
要是鲍尔撬开了帕维尔的嘴...
If Bauer gets Pavel to talk...
但目前来说  长官
But at the moment, sir,
您仍然可以否认一切
you still have complete deniability.
所有的决定都是泰勒总统作出的
President Taylor made all the decisions.
我觉得现在是时候
I think the time has come
让您远离是非了
for you to distance yourself from this mess.
虽然非常的遗憾  长官
It's regrettable, sir, deeply so,
但我觉得这是目前对您最好的选择
but I believe it's what's best for you.
你...
You...
二十分钟后
20 minutes from now,
总统的新闻秘书
the president's press secretary
就要发表一份声明
is going to make an announcement.
她会宣布...
She will say...
我已成为总统政府的一员
I have become part of the president's team,
在让和平进程功德圆满的过程中
and-and I have been indispensable in bringing this peace process
我发挥了无可取代的作用
to a successful close.
长官  请原谅我告诉您这是个坏主意
Sir, may I say that that is a bad idea?
您现在得远离是非
You need to distance yourself.
什么  你一直在用那个词
What? You keep using that phrase.
什么叫远离是非
What-What does distance myself mean?
是要我偷偷溜走吗
Do I just slink away?
有些情况是我们始料未及的
There were circumstances we couldn't have anticipated.
也就是鲍尔
Namely Bauer.
那就找到他  干掉他
Well, then, we find Bauer, and we neutralize him.
我们从幕后走向了台前  杰森
We're public now, Jason.
我们致力于此
We're committed.
而且我已经...  是我们
And I have worked... We...
我们已经付诸了太多心血
We have worked too hard
不能让其付之东流
just to throw this all away.
你明白了吗
Do you understand?
-当然  长官  但是帕维尔...  -不
- Yes, of course, sir, but Pavel... - No.
帕维尔是出色的战士
Pavel is a good soldier.
无论鲍尔怎么拷问  他都不会招供的
He won't talk, whatever Bauer does to him.
我让你进反恐小组  是有原因的  杰森
I, uh... I put you at CTU, Jason, for a reason.
他们拥有丰富的资源
They have huge resources.
而你有勇有谋
You have intelligence and tenacity.
利用好这一切  找到鲍尔
You use those capabilities. Find Bauer.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
-我会亲自前往现场  -很好
- I'll head down to the scene myself. - Good.
随时向我报告
Keep me posted.
他想继续下去
He wants to move forward.
他真的明白现在的状况吗
Does he understand what actually happened?
是的  但他说我们仍有选择的余地
Yes, but he says we still have options.
告诉我  你会跟我同舟共济
I need to know you're with me on this.
是的  同舟共济
Yes. Yes, I'm with you.
好  我要出去了
Good. I'm heading out.
我会清理现场留下的一切俄罗斯人的证据
I'll clean up the scene, remove all trace of the Russians,
然后设法找到鲍尔的下落
and get on Bauer's trail.
我会带上反恐小组的特警队
I'll take CTU SWAT with me.
命令纽约警局以商店为圆心警戒周围两个街区
Tell NYPD to put a two-block perimeter around the store.
没有我的命令不得让任何人出入
No one goes in or out without my say-so.
我该以什么理由命令他们
What reason do I give them?
如有任何人阻挠  就以白宫的名义行使权力
Anyone gives you a hard time, invoke the White House.
有杰克帮手的线索了吗
Any luck with Jack's associates?
没有  即使排除死去的人
No. Even discounting dead people,
以及外国人
and people from foreign countries,
还是得花上几个小时
it's still going to take hours.
我可以缩小范围
I think I can narrow it down.
我刚监听到市中心特纳百货公司
I just picked up a 911 call
打来的一个报警电话
from Turner's in Midtown.
那里发生了枪击事件  造成了人员伤亡
There was a shoot-out, people killed.
我成功进入了那家商店的监控系统
I managed to get into the store's security system.
天哪
Oh, my God.
是杰克
That's Jack.
他们想杀他
They're trying to kill him.
是的  不过计划没有成功
Yeah, that part of the plan didn't go so well.
我对监控录像从枪战开始前五分钟
I tagged the footage 5 minutes before
到结束后五分钟做了标记
to 5 minutes after the shooting.
如果我们对录像中的人进行面部识别
If we run facial recognition on the camera feeds...
就能与杰克帮手们的数据库进行比对
We can match it to the database of Jack's associates,
也许就能找出杰克是和谁联手了
maybe find out who he's working with.
多谢  阿洛
Thanks, Arlo.
不客气
No problem.
把那些录像画面复制到我屏幕上
Copy the camera footage to my screen.
我会把一半的人员档案发给你
I'll send you half the personnel files.
安全  我们走
We're clear. Let's go.
快走
Let's go.
快掏空你口袋里的东西
Empty your pockets right now here.
坐下
Take a seat.
在这我们暂时是安全的
We'll be safe here for a while.
杰克  我们时间不多
Jack? We don't have much time.
脱下你的外套
Take off your coat.
快
Now!
你刚杀的那些人...
Those people you killed...
你准备好要杀他们  是吗
you were ready for them, weren't you?
你早知道他们会来的
You knew they were coming.
是的
Yeah.
那你  你早知道他们会窃听我们的电话
So you... you knew they'd be listening to our phone call.
是这样吗
Isn't that right?
你利用我引他们出来  对吗
You used me to draw them out, right?
是的
That's right.
我可能会死在那里
I could have been killed back there!
你没死
You weren't.
快捡起来
Now, pick it up.
我叫你把它捡起来
I said pick it up!
你说过要给我证据
What about the evidence you said you'd tell me?
那也是谎言  是不是
Was that a lie, too?
不是
No.
证据在这张记忆卡里
The evidence is on this memory card.
你看到视频  就会知道一切是真的
When you see it, you'll know it's real.
拿着
Take it.
我搭档会带你去个地方  给你看
My partner's gonna take you somewhere to show it to you.
我很抱歉  是我不得已而为之
I'm sorry things had to play out like this.
我别无选择
I didn't see another choice.
那你接着要干什么
What are you gonna do?
把双手放到背后  快
Put your hands behind your back. Now!
不要这么做  求你  你不想这么做的
Don't do this, please. You don't want to do this.
把她带到储藏室
Take her to the storeroom.
不  我哪也不去
No, I'm not going anywhere.
求你了  你不能这样做
Please, you cannot do this.
我给你的证据
The evidence I gave you
没能告诉我沃什是怎么卷入这勾当的
doesn't tell me how Walsh was involved.
他能告诉我
He will.
-走吧  -不
- Come on. - No.
你不能这样做
You cannot do this this way!
坐在那
Sit over there.
春田造M1A式步枪
Springfield, M1A rifle.
点308口径弹药
.308 round.
约四小时之前
You know, about four hours ago,
我的一个朋友  一个非常要好的朋友
I had a friend of mine-- very good friend--
名叫蕾妮·沃克  就死在这型号的枪下
named Renee Walker was killed by a rifle just like that.
去死吧
Go to hell.
我先送你一程
You first.
刺杀哈桑的行动已万事俱备
The hit on Hassan is all arranged.
巴扎耶夫及其手下正在处理一切
Bazhaev and his people are taking care of everything.
你只能和我单线联系
You talk to no one but me.
就此打住
We're done here.
哈桑死之前不许再联系我
Don't contact me again until Hassan is dead.
老实和你说
To be honest with you,
蕾妮·沃克不只是我的普通朋友
Renee Walker was more than just my friend.
你应该已经知道了  不是吗
But you already know that, don't you?
你看到我们在我公寓的卧室里
Because you saw us in the bedroom of my apartment.
这么说  要么是你狙击手的枪法太烂
Now, you're either not very good at what you do...
要么就是你想让她生不如死
or you wanted her to suffer.
因为以这把枪的射程
Because with that rifle from that range,
轻而易举就能一枪毙命
it was an easy kill shot.
但你却
But instead,
把枪眼对准她...
you shot her...
就是这里
right there...
心脏以下两英寸
two inches below her heart,
让她慢慢放血
so she would bleed out slowly.
我看着她
I watched her
因为血液慢慢填满肺部
gasping for air...
而艰难呼吸
as the blood slowly filled her lungs.
在痛苦中死去
She died in agony,
除非你告诉我  我想知道的
which is exactly what I'm gonna make you do
否则我也让你尝尝这滋味
unless you tell me what I want to know.
快说
Start talking to me!
你想知道  是不是我杀了你女朋友
You want to know I killed your girlfriend?
是我杀的她
I killed her.
是我杀了你那婊子
I kill your bitch!
求你  求你  你得让他住手  求你
Please... please, you've got to stop him. Please.
你要得到答案  他会给他的
He needs answers, and he's gonna get 'em.
我能用这向大众证明  这足够了
I can use this. There's enough here.
我不需要更多了
I don't need any more.
告诉他  我不需要更多了  求你了
Tell him I don't need any more. Please.
你哪儿也不能去
You're not going anywhere.
请让开  让开  让开
Move aside. Move. Move.
请离开尸体
Please step back from the bodies.
我宣布这里是反恐小组罪案现场
This is now a CTU crime scene.
我要所有从这些人身上搜到的武器和文件
I need all weapons and documents you found on these people.
长官  这是所有我们找到的
This is all we got, sir.
但所有人身上都没有身份证明
None of them had I.D.s on them.
这就是我们在找的人
This is the man we're looking for.
他名叫杰克·鲍尔
His name is Jack Bauer.
现在  你们分头去找他
Now, you need to spread out
检查每层楼面和每个出口
and check every floor and every exit.
他手上有人质  所以不会走远
He has a hostage with him, so he won't have gotten far.
鲍尔携带武器  是个非常危险的人物
Bauer's armed and extremely dangerous,
如果你们不想下场和这些人一样
so if you don't want to end up like these people,
见到他格杀勿论
shoot on sight.
我们走
Let's go.
听好了
Hey.
你醒了  我们接着玩如何
So, why don't we start this again.
我已知道是你杀了蕾妮·沃克
I already know that you killed Renee Walker.
我现在要知道的是...
What I want to know...
俄罗斯政府里面
is the name...
那头下命令的
of the Russian pig
俄国猪的
inside your government
名字
...that gave the order.
告诉我名字  我会给你个痛快
Give me a name, and I'll end this quickly.
我说话算话
I give you my word.
你觉得你了解痛苦是吗
You think you know about pain?
现在才刚开始
You don't know anything yet.
告诉我你们政府里
Give me the name of the person
想要蕾妮·沃克死的
inside your government
那个人的名字
who wanted Renee Walker dead!
告诉我名字
Give me the name!
是谁下的命令
Who gave the order?!
你们政府里的谁
Who inside your government
想要置蕾妮·沃克于死地
wanted Renee Walker dead?
你只要把名字告诉我
All you got to do is give me the name!
你们这些人蠢到家了
You people are so stupid.
蕾妮·沃克对你们不是什么威胁
Renee Walker wasn't a threat to you.
她任务完成了  完成了  我们退出行动了
Her work was finished. She was done. We were out.
你们要做的  就是别再来找我们麻烦
All you had to do is leave us alone.
你们为什么就不能放过我们呢
Now, why couldn't you just leave us alone?
我要那个给你命令
I want the name of the person
让你开枪的人的名字
who gave the order to pull the trigger!
是谁下的命令
Who gave the order?!
快说
Now!
是我一个人干的
Did it on my own!
你在说谎  你只是个无名小卒
You're lying. You're nothing.
你没有权力
You didn't have the authority.
我要那人的名字
I want the name!
告诉我那人的名字
Give me the name!
我的名字叫帕维尔·托卡列夫
My name is Pavel Tokarev.
这个也没用
This isn't working.
你的手机SIM卡在哪里
Where's the SIM card for your phone?
手机卡在哪里
Where's the SIM card?!
你会扔在哪里
Where'd you drop it?
你这蠢货  你吞了下去
You dumb bastard, you swallowed it.
你刚吞了下去
You swallowed it.
这一下是为了我的朋友
This is for my friend.
-你们找到什么了  -这边没人  长官
- What do you got? - This side's clear, sir.
好  那还有一个员工通道
Fine. There's another service hallway.
检查那边所有的员工通道
Check all the service hallways over there.
确保都是锁着的
Make sure they're locked down.
你们  我要你们上去  到三楼
You guys, I want you to go up there, stay on the third floor.
马上去
Do it now.
您所拨打的是查尔斯·罗根总统的移动电话
You've reached the mobile number of President Charles Logan.
我们不能马上为您接通
We can't take your call right now,
但如果您留下姓名和电话号码
but if you leave your name and number,
我们将尽快给您回电
we'll get back to you as soon as we can.